hello and welcome back to new everyday
你好，欢迎回到新的 日常生活
I'm Carrie and my name is Jen and on
我是嘉莉，我的名字是仁和继续
today's show we're talking about some
今天的节目我们正在谈论一些
prickly situations so stay tuned for
带刺的情况下， 敬请关注
more life in the desert on our road trip
在我们的客场之旅中沙漠中更多的生活
welcome back we're so glad that you've
欢迎回来，我们很高兴，你已经
tuned in again this week we are
调谐本周再度我们
continuing our discussion about our
继续我们对我们的讨论
crazy road trip that we took to the
疯狂的公路旅行， 我们带到了
United States landing landed in Vegas
美国着陆降落在拉斯维加斯
rented a hippie man travel to la camp
租了一个嬉皮士旅行到拉营
through the desert was amazing yeah the
通过沙漠是惊人的是的
desert was actually cold the desert was
沙漠竟是冷沙漠 是
cold I thought Sam it's hot first
冷，我认为山姆是第一热的
morning I thought my hands were going to
早上我以为我的手会去
fall off oh yeah it was bad but man we
脱落哦，是的，它是坏的，但我们的人
lit up our propane stove when we cooked
当我们煮熟时点燃我们的丙烷炉
and it's just so satisfying to camp you
这让你很难受
never gone camping you need to do it
从来没有去野营，你需要做到这一点
right what who can't stop the cab for
正确的是谁不能阻止 驾驶室
but she did so great I did I was very
但她做得非常棒，我做得非常棒
impressed in our camper van but it's
留在我们的露营车上，但它是
because now campervan no scorpions no
因为现在campervan 没有蝎子没有
scorpions no snakes the Bears can't get
熊不能得到蝎子没有蛇
at you there are firm walls all around
在你身边，周围有坚固的墙壁
you drive in you park it there is no
你开车在你停车没有
shimming it up there's no getting out
把它踢起来没有出去
putting it out packing it up when the
把它收拾起来的时候
rain comes bring it on like I did try
雨会带来它像我一样尝试
and put together a table you said
并把你说的一张桌子放在一起
anytime you did it's funny what's
任何时候你都这么做很有趣
talking so not everything worked out
说话并非一切都奏效
perfectly but we did have another
完美，但我们确实有另一个
amazing adventure down into the toya
惊人的冒险进入toya
gardens yes add the joshua tree national
花园是添加约书亚树国家
tree national park in southern
南部的树国家公园
california yeah and the toy garden the
加利福尼亚州和玩具园
Choya cactus it's a family of cactus ki
Choya仙人掌它是仙人掌ki家庭
kak ty kak ty chance done some research
kak ty kak ty 机会做了一些研究
and it was like a hundred thousand of
它就像十万
these plants owe money in the bottom of
这些工厂欠钱
this family thing so when we drove down
这个家庭的事情，所以当我们开车下来
what happened was when there was a
发生了什么事是什么时候有一个
torrent of water going down into this
水流入此
valley they carried well brings water
他们携带的山谷带来了水
yeah and there were some cacti there and
是的，那里有一些仙人掌
they spread their seeds in the torrents
他们在种子中传播种子
of water would then pick up the seeds
的水会收拾种子
spread it out into a fan like I was
像我一样分散成一个粉丝
talking about last week and spread the
谈论上周和传播
season so consequently there was a
因此有一个季节
garden like a practically a forest
花园几乎像一片森林
these teddy bear Choya yes teddy bear
这些玩具熊Choya是泰迪熊
Choya it spelt CH 0 lla and I have said
Choya拼写CH 0 lla，我已经说过了
it several different ways to Walla Walla
它有几种不同的方式给Walla Walla
tola today she was like actual yet Toya
今天的托拉她真的很像托雅
so it is pronounced Choya yeah and but
所以它是发音Choya耶和但
they're anything but Teddy bear-like
他们只是泰迪熊式的东西
because the the spines would you call
因为你会打电话给你
them spine pokies pokies scientific name
他们的脊柱pokies pokies学名
pokies the pokies on them are like quite
pokies对他们的pokies很像
long oh yeah and they are designed in
很长时间哦，是的，他们是在设计
such a way that when you rub up against
这种方式，当你碰到
them then they immediately like to stick
他们然后立即喜欢坚持
to you they're like velcro they're like
对你来说他们就像魔术贴一样
velcro like slightest touch they're like
魔术贴像他们喜欢的丝毫触摸
the best velcro ever yeah and one of the
最好的魔术贴是耶和其中一个
one of the videos that I watched on the
我观看过的其中一个视频
garden the guy said this is not the
花园里的那个人说这不是
garden to run through naked at night
花园在晚上裸体穿过
it's like Howie ethylene because what's
这就像Howie乙烯，因为它是什么
interesting is you think of a teddy bear
有趣的是你想​​起一只泰迪熊
think cute cuddly I want to hug it right
想可爱可爱，我想拥抱它的权利
cuz but these they stick to you at just
因为这些他们只是坚持你
the slightest touch so I think at one
一点点触觉，所以我认为在一个
point we just simply went off the beaten
点我们只是简单地打败了
trenton and not even far like just
特伦顿， 甚至不像只是
slightly to look at a plant and one got
稍微看看一个植物，一个得到了
on my foot and you didn't even know it
在我的脚上，你甚至不知道它
in fact someone came up behind her and
实际上有人在她后面来了
said Jack I not judging or name that
杰克说我没有判断或者说出这个名字
weird nerd unless she was like hey are
奇怪的书呆子，除非她喜欢嘿
you Jen from you every day Oh didn't
你每天都会从你那里噢没有
happen did not happen but if you ever
发生没有发生，但如果你曾经
see us in public come and say hi because
在公共场合看到我们，并且因为我们说你好
we really want to meet you everyone
我们真的很想 见到你们每个人
who's watching anyways so this little
无论如何，这些人都在看
Choya thing and they're called jumping
乔亚的东西，他们被称为跳跃
Choya because it seems like these little
乔亚，因为它看起来很小
pods which are actually the seeds that
豆荚实际上是种子
break away and that's how they germinate
脱离，这就是他们萌芽的方式
or spread so this little thing stuck to
或传播，所以这个小东西卡住
her and she didn't even know it someone
她和她甚至不知道这个人
came up behind her it was like hey you
出现在她后面，就像是 你
got a guy yes on your foot yeah and then
有一个人是你的脚是的， 然后
Kari at one point like cuz I'm as I'm
卡里在一个点上，因为我是我
getting it off of me Carrie actually got
把它从我身上拿开， 嘉莉居然得到了
one on her foot and she's like fling it
一个在她的脚上，她就像扔掉它
off playing it off a crab and what was
把它从一只螃蟹上拿下来，那是什么
interesting about the
有趣的
teddy bear Toya is that if you get the
泰迪熊东亚是如果你得到了
barbs or pokey things Robbie can you
倒钩或罗比可以帮助你的事情
blend that you know you can be the
混合，你知道你可以成为
intellectual one for this show and put
知识分子为这个节目并且投入
up the real name whatever they are
不管他们是什么，都要记住真名
quills they go into your skin and they
羽毛球进入你的皮肤和他们
said they're quite difficult to take out
说他们很难拿出
why it must be the little thing on the
为什么它一定是那件小事
ends the barbed end gets in and if you
结束倒钩的末端进入，如果你
do not take it out properly then
那么不要把它拿出来
actually infection can occur and you
实际上感染可能会发生，你
need medical attention I'm like because
需要医疗照顾我就像是因为
you look at them and you and they really
你看看他们，你和他们真的
are quite beautiful to look at yeah and
是非常漂亮的看着是啊和
they look soft in a way because they're
他们看起来很软，因为他们是
totally covered right yeah but not even
完全覆盖是的，但不是
soft even looking at them on the side of
软甚至在他们身边看着他们
the path I was like I just want to touch
我就像我只想碰触的路径
them and I wanted to touch them mostly
他们和我想主要碰他们
because I knew I couldn't you know like
因为我知道我不知道
I just want to I just want to touch it
我只想我只想触摸它
so hard not to it was so hard not to but
所以很难不要这么辛苦
they were so sneaky like because neither
他们太狡猾了，因为都不是
one of us knew that we had them on us
我们中的一个人知道我们有他们
and it reminded us of the fact that the
它提醒了我们事实
enemy appears like an angel of light
敌人看起来像光明天使
like just so sneaky and I was looking at
就像我偷偷摸摸地看着
a passage from Hebrews this is Hebrews 2
来自希伯来书的这段是希伯来书2
and it said so we must be more careful
它说，所以我们必须更加小心
to follow what we were taught then we
遵循我们所教的，然后我们
will not stray away from the truth and
不会偏离真相和事实
it just these these little jumping teddy
它就是这些小跳跃泰迪熊
bears made me think because they're so
熊让我觉得，因为他们是如此
sneaky that you know they they latch
偷偷摸摸，你知道他们锁定
onto you and they wait for you to carry
到你身上，他们等着你携带
them away and they're smoother designed
他们走了，他们更平滑的设计
for that like that's how they germinate
因为这就是他们如何发芽
and that's how they spread to other
这就是他们如何传播给其他人
areas and it protects them against
地区，并保护他们免受
predators as well as well for being so
捕食者以及如此
spiky but it just got me thinking about
尖刺，但它让我思考
the enemy and how sneaky he is and how
敌人 ，他是多么的狡猾以及如何
he can sort of just you know we can
他可以只是你知道我们可以
unknowingly just brush up against
在不知不觉中刷到了
something and think oh no or perfectly
一些东西，并认为不，或完美
fine because I didn't actually do what
很好，因为我实际上没做什么
ever i thought i might do and when we a
曾经我以为我会做，当我们做
little bit when we were in vegas i said
我们在 拉斯维加斯时说过一点点
to carry my eyes are seeing things I
拎着我的眼睛看到我的东西
don't want to see because what happens
不想看到，因为会发生什么
is those images go in right and I can
那些图像是正确的，我可以
think well I haven't meditated of
好好想想我没有沉思过
Germany yeah but you know those things
德国是的，但你知道这些事情
can go in they can come back and in
可以进去他们可以 回来进去
dreams and just cause you to have so
梦想，只是让你有这样的
much like angst I find and I really
很像我发现的和我真的很焦虑
thought about those jumping cactuses and
想到那些跳跃的仙人掌和
and just as a as an object lesson for
并且只是作为对象的教训
how the enemy can sort of attach itself
敌人可以如何附加自己
into our lives like just get involved in
进入我们的生活就像参与进来一样
and be carried along right and do not
并 随身携带 ，而不是
even know and not even know and so
甚至知道甚至不知道等等
needless to say when I finished being in
当我完成时不用说
Vegas I was like okay Lord could you
拉斯维加斯我很喜欢主可以
just take care of my thoughts would you
只是照顾我的想法会不会
just you know get rid of all those
只是你知道摆脱所有这些
sticky things that might be sticking to
粘性的东西，可能会坚持
me cuz I don't want them to I don't want
我因为我不想他们我不想要
to you know get an infection spiritually
到你知道精神上感染
yeah and and that's where we met another
是的，那就是我们遇到的另一个地方
Park Ranger Ranger Beth I'll show you a
公园游侠游侠贝丝我会告诉你一个
picture of her she said that that was
她的照片说，那 是
okay and Beth kind of explained a lot
好吧，贝丝有很多解释
more about the cactus and the types of
更多关于仙人掌和类型的信息
birds that actually live in the cactus
实际上生活在仙人掌中的鸟
and what the danger is being associated
以及与之相关的危险
with it she was our guide and that's
有了它，她就成了我们的指南，就是这样
again like the Word of God and we had a
再次像上帝的话语，我们有一个
map with us actually to tell us about
与我们实际地图告诉我们
the different things of the garden and
花园和花园的不同之处
help us to see the beauty in it but also
帮助我们看到 它的美丽，但也
to be warned about some of the aspects
要警告一些方面
of the cactus garden that we should
我们应该的仙人掌花园
avoid mm-hmm and psalm 119 105 says your
避免mm-hmm和psalm 119 105说你的
word is a lamp unto my feet and a light
我的脚和光是一盏灯
unto my path and that's the purpose of
到我的路上，这就是我的目的
the scriptures to illuminate things in
圣经照亮事物
our life yes and and and the Bible says
我们的生活是和，圣经说
to purify yourself out of reverence for
为了崇拜你而净化自己
God Jesus says if you love me you obey
上帝耶稣说，如果你爱我，你就服从
me you put away the things that the
我把你的东西收起来了
things that are an ascend that's so
这是一个提升的事情
easily entangles and then run the race
容易纠缠然后跑比赛
with perseverance and that's why we need
坚持不懈，这就是我们需要的原因
that guide in our life may the Holy
我们生活中的向导可能是圣洁的
Spirit will need the scripture to
精神将需要圣经来
illuminate the path that we can walk
照亮我们可以走的路径
clearly yes and in
显然是和中
the end it's less painful oh yeah cuz
最终它不那么痛苦哦，是的
they said don't go off the path not only
他们说不只是走上了道路
is it bad for nature but it's going to
它是坏的性质，但它会
hurt you yeah and I we were hiking
伤害你是我和我们徒步旅行
another mountain trail and I wanted this
另一条山路，我想要这个
really cool picture of a cactus with the
真的很酷的仙人掌的图片
mountains in the background and I did
山脉在背景中，我做到了
get it but at a cost because I went off
得到它，但有代价，因为我离开了
the path and I bent down and I actually
我的路和弯曲，我实际上
put my arm in a cactus and I don't know
把我的手臂放在仙人掌里，我不知道
if you can see the quills that were in
如果你能看到那些羽毛
my arm but I had to pull them out and it
我的胳膊，但我不得不拉出来 ，并
was painful I'm video of that oh dear do
是痛苦的我是那个哦，亲爱的视频
you yes that likes us so I just learned
你是喜欢我们，所以我才学会了
something very important if you see a
如果你看到一个非常重要的东西
cactus don't touch it or lay on it
仙人掌不要碰它或躺在它上面
because they will stick in you as you
因为他们会像你一样粘在你身上
can see here very dangerous oh that's
可以看到这里非常危险哦
all i have to say so yeah lesson learned
所有我必须说，所以是的经验教训
and it was it was ouchie like it hurt
它就像它受伤一样
like as I'm video taping her you're
就像我在录像给她看你一样
thinking why did she put the camera down
思考为什么她把相机放下
and help her it's better to get it on
并帮助她最好把它打开
film but she's like and at one point you
电影，但她喜欢，并在某一点上你
were kind of like some of them are my
有点像他们中的一些人是我的
coke but some of them were my skin yeah
可乐，但其中一些是我的皮肤是啊
and like that hurt was Ali yeah so it
就像那个伤害是阿里是这样
was very interesting like stay like they
非常有趣，就像他们一样
were very clear like stay on ah but what
非常清楚，像留在啊，但什么
was also interesting was that the
也很有趣的是，
Rangers they appreciated the diversity
他们对流浪者表示赞赏
they wanted to preserve that and as we
他们想要保留这一点，因为我们
were hiking through Joshua Tree we saw a
正在通过约书亚树徒步旅行，我们看到了
plaque about a woman named Minerva whoit
关于一名名为Minerva whoit的女人的牌匾
whoit Minerva Hoyt who was this woman
谁是Minerva Hoyt谁是这个女人
actually from Mississippi mm-hmm very
实际上来自密西西比州毫米非常
well-to-do woman actually you think what
富裕的女人其实你认为是什么
was she doing oh yes yeah she was a very
是她在做，是的，她是 一个非常
well-to-do woman from a well-to-do
富裕的女人从富裕到做
family who had moved to Southern
家人搬到了南方
California oh and she got attracted by
哦，她被吸引了
the beauty of the desert yes appreciated
沙漠的美丽是赞赏
the diversity that was there and saw the
在那里的多样性，看到了
beauty that no one else saw and maybe
美丽，没有人看到，也许
you can speak a little bit more to that
你会说 更多的到一点点
Jenna no way you've done a little bit of
詹娜没有办法，你已经做了一点点
reading on her well she yeah I
读她的好，她是啊我
appreciated the beauty she saw the
欣赏她看到的美景
beauty in the desert when so many people
当沙漠中有这么多人的美丽
as she said we're digging it up and
因为她说我们正在挖掘它
burning it and running
燃烧它并运行
over it she was like no there's beauty
在它之上，她就像没有美丽
here and so she actually petitioned
在这里， 她实际上请求了
President Roosevelt right to make it a
罗斯福总统有权做到这一点
national part that they needed to
他们需要全国部分
protect that land the vegetation in the
保护土地上的植被
desert there for future generations
沙漠有后代
because it was important there was
因为这很重要
beauty there and and it challenged me as
在那里的美丽和它挑战我
I read that because we had been talking
我读过那篇文章是因为我们一直 在说话
we have been talking a lot about how
我们一直在谈论如何
there's life in the desert there's life
在沙漠中有生命存在
in the desert but it takes I want to say
在沙漠中，但我想说
a keen eye to see it like are we
敏锐的目光看到它就像是我们
actually looking for the Oasis's are we
其实我们是在寻找绿洲的
actually looking for the the sources of
实际上寻找的来源
water or the beauty around us are we
水或我们周围的美是我们
looking for how God has the provisions
寻找神如何拥有这些规定
God has given us and she was seeing that
上帝赐给我们，她看到了
she saw the beauty even though you know
即使你知道，她也看到了美丽
everybody thought well it's a desert
大家都认为这是一片沙漠
there's nothing good that could come out
没有什么好东西可以出来
yes people often only see how a
是的，人们往往只看到一个
landscape can benefit them directly and
景观可以直接和他们受益
I saw a picture it was assignment that
我看到了 这是一个 分配 的图片
said that essentially that people wanted
说基本上人们想要的
to to take advantage of of the geography
以利用地理
there only if it could bring them in
只有这样才能把他们带进来
some money through that area was really
通过这个领域的一些钱真的是
affected by the gold rush to if people
受淘金热影响的人如何
are running to dig up the gold and they
正在奔跑挖掘黄金和他们
start a lot of minds and whatever it
开始思考很多，不管它
reminded me of was in Genesis 1 where
让我想起了在创世记1 里的地方
God actually you know after he created
上帝在 他创造 后，其实你是知道的
male and female he said god bless it and
男性和女性，他说上帝保佑它 和
said to have many children and grow in
据说有很多孩子并且成长
number so this is Genesis 128 from the
数字，所以这是从创世记128
new century version fill the earth and
新世纪的版本填补了地球和
be its master rule over the fish in the
成为它对鱼类的主宰
sea and over the birds in the sky and
海和鸟儿在天空和
over every living thing that moves on
在每一个继续前进的生物上
the earth and it says look God said look
地球，它说，看上帝说的样子
I've given you all the plants that have
我已经给你所有的植物了
grain for seed and all the trees whose
粮食为种子和所有的树木的
fruit have seed in them they will be
水果有种子，他们会
food for you I have given all the green
给你的食物我给了所有的绿色
plants as food for every animal and
植物作为每个动物和食物的食物
every bird of the air and every small
空气和每一个细小的每只鸟
crawling animal and it happened and it's
爬行动物，它发生了，它
like God gifted us the earth and we are
就像上帝赐予我们地球一样，我们是
to be stewards of it we're supposed to
成为我们应该担任的管家
look after it and just like Minerva
照顾它，就像密涅瓦一样
looked at this land in Joshua Tree she's
她在约书亚树看着这片土地
like we need to look after this we can't
就像我们需要照顾这个我们不能
let people just run over it and just
让人们只是忽略它而已
like the two Rangers
就像两个流浪者一样
said no look at the beauty see the
说不看美女看
beauty look beyond just you know driving
除了你知道开车之外的美丽外观
by it like actually get to know it it it
通过它就像真正了解它它
really challenged me because I remember
因为我记得，真的给我挑战
Carrie it showed me a video about this
嘉莉给 我看了一个关于这个的视频
young woman who basically was trying to
年轻女子基本上正在尝试
live a garbage free life she did it for
过着她为之奋斗的无垃圾生活
two years like like no garbage except a
两年， 就像没有垃圾一样
mason jar of like random string and yeah
梅森罐子的随机字符串和是啊
something she didn't know what to do
她不知道该怎么做
with yeah and I just it really really
与耶和我真的真的
impacted me because I thought okay we're
影响了我， 因为我 认为我们没关系
called to be to Stewart the land so what
打电话给斯图尔特的土地等等
about recycling what about you know
关于回收你知道的事情
watching the things you know being
看着你知道的东西
careful what the things that we buy in
小心我们买的东西
too much packaging because it does that
太多的包装，因为它这样做
just go into a landfill which you know
只要进入你知道的垃圾填埋场
we're gonna get this big chemical he a
我们会得到这个大化学品他
feat that we're gonna eat eventually
我们最终会吃的 壮举
yeah opener food and down and and so it
是 开胃菜和下来，等等
challenged me like how am I being a good
向我挑战，好像我是 一个好人
steward of the land like even down the
这个地方的管家就像下来
car that I dry and being excessive with
我干的和过度的汽车
driving and using up you know gasps and
驾驶和使用起来你知道喘气和
and I'm still working on that I don't
而且我还在努力，我没有
have a final answer I feel like there's
有一个最终的答案我觉得有
a healthy middle ground because there's
一个健康的中间地带，因为有
some people who take it too extreme and
有些人认为它太极端了
and can't even enjoy the things that are
甚至不能享受那些事情
before them yes and there are some
在他们面前是的，还有一些
people who are like and even Christians
喜欢甚至是基督徒的人
who say well you know what this world is
谁说你知道这个世界是什么
not my home anyway I'm just here for a
无论如何，我的家不是我在这里
short time and not really consider the
时间短，并没有真正考虑
people who are coming after the exact
那些在确切的事情之后来的人
same thing to think about yeah yeah yeah
同样的事情想想是啊是的
I was challenged by that video 2 i'll
我受到了视频2的挑战
put a link for you to the youtube video
为你提供一个链接到YouTube视频
of the interview with this woman that it
对这个女人的采访就是这样
was really challenged by so yeah and
真的受到了挑战，所以是的
every so-and-so looking at minerva and
每一个如此如此看着密涅瓦和
how she stepped up to protect the land
她如何加强保护土地
and i'm so glad because now we we were
我很高兴， 因为现在我们是
able to go and enjoy it and I was just
能够去享受它，我只是
so blessed by her for thought so I guess
所以我猜想她是有福的
that's what I'm wanting is that the Lord
这就是我想要的是主
would give me for thought in how to look
会给我思考如何看待
after the space he has given me to look
在他给我看的空间之后
after so
之后如此
that you know future generations whether
你知道后世是否
they're mine or someone else's can then
他们是我的，或者是别人的
enjoy the same space yeah it's really
享受同样的空间是真的
cool on the outside of a farm that I
我在一个农场的外面冷静下来
lived at my great-grandmother planted Oh
住在我的曾祖母种的哦
golly I've dropped the name it's a
很高兴我放弃了它的名字
flower that clematis and and it has been
花，铁线莲和它一直
climbing up the side of the house for
爬上房子的一侧
over a hundred years no way and it's
一百年没有办法，这是
beautiful and I'm so thankful that she
美丽，我非常感谢， 她
had the forethought to plant it and that
有预谋的种植它和那个
the oncoming generations have taken care
即将到来的世代已经照顾好了
of it so that we can enjoy the same
这样我们可以享受同样的享受
beauty plus more that she enjoyed and to
美丽加上她喜欢的和更多
the fact that my cousin that lives in
我的堂兄弟居住的事实
that home and he's actually wanting to
那个家，他真的想要
build like an arbor so that it can grow
建造像一个乔木，使其可以成长
up and over it so that future
为了未来而做好准备
generations can continue to enjoy that
世代可以继续享受
climbing cactus or climbing clematis and
攀爬仙人掌或攀登铁线莲
so you know as we are to be good
所以你知道我们是好的
stewards of the land it's it's not only
这不仅是它的土地管家
for our own benefit but it is so that
为了我们自己的利益，但它是如此
our future generations have something to
我们的后代有一些东西
enjoy yeah so yeah and very cool yeah
享受是啊，所以耶和非常酷耶
the I've dropped the name again Toya
我已经把名字再次放弃了Toya
Toya the choice to cholla or oh yeah a
Toya选择cholla或噢是啊
lot of lessons to be learned i mean oh
很多的 经验教训，我的意思是哦
yes much more that we could talk about
是的，我们 可以谈论 更多
as far as the life in that area of the
至于该地区 的生活
desert including like a desert ran like
沙漠包括像沙漠一样奔跑
a little bird that lives in the cactus
一只住在仙人掌里的小鸟
mrs. home their finds refuge their
太太。在他们的家寻找避难所
protection from predators yes when we
防止掠食者是当我们
could talk about that for a long time
可以谈，很长一段 时间
but yeah we just encourage you to take
但是， 我们只是鼓励你参加
stock of your life and maybe there's
你的生命存量，也许有
something some changes that you could
你可以做一些改变
make to be more conscientious about the
使...更加认真
waste that we're making so maybe I'll
我们正在做的浪费也许会
just pray for us Jen sure father thank
只为我们祈祷珍确定父亲谢谢
you so much for this earth that you've
你为这个世界而努力
made it's so diverse and beautiful thank
让它变得如此多样和美丽的感谢
you for the world around us thank you
你为我们周围的世界感谢你
for the places that each of us live in
为我们每个人住的地方
and I know a lot of our viewers live in
我知道很多观众都住在这里
other countries that you have also made
其他国家，你也做了
so incredible I pray that you'd open our
如此令人难以置信的我祈祷，你会打开我们的
eyes Lord to the things around us that
眼睛主对我们身边的事情，
we can celebrate the view
我们可以庆祝这个观点
that you have made and realized that it
你已经做出并意识到它
declares your glory thank you for the
宣布你的荣耀感谢你的
diversity in this world would you help
这个世界的多样性会对 你 有所帮助
us to be good stewards help us to
我们是好管家帮我们
advocate when we need to advocate and I
主张我们需要倡导的时候和我
just thank you for our viewers I'll
只是谢谢我们的观众
always just commit this week to you it's
一直就在本周提交给您， 这是
in the name of Jesus we pray amen amen
我们以耶稣的名义为阿门祈祷
thank you for tuning in again yes and we
感谢您再次调整是和我们
probably have a couple more shows to
可能会有更多的节目
show you about our trip and some of our
告诉你我们的 旅行和我们的一些
adventures in the United States and we
在美国和我们的冒险
hope that you'll tune in pop on over to
希望你能收听到
our website new everyday TV click our
我们的网站新的每日电视点击我们
partners page scroll down we've got so
合作伙伴页面向下滚动，我们已经有了
many people partnering with us so many
很多人和我们合作很多
businesses partnering with us which we
企业与我们合作，我们
are so thankful for thanks to Robbie
非常感谢罗比
Ferguson and category 5 TV for hosting
弗格森和5类电视主持
this show and for editing and producing
这个节目和编辑和制作
it we're so grateful and also so
我们非常感激，也是如此
grateful for you for tuning in yes so we
感谢您的调整是的，所以我们
encourage you to stay on the path this
鼓励你留在这条路上
week and we'll see you here again next
一周，我们会在下一次再见到你
week same time same place it's on the
一周同一时间在同一个地方
internet it's hard to say where you're
互联网很难说你在哪里
going to be watching it true I've
我会看着它真实
watched in different places i actually
我实际上在不同的地方观看
have watched us on vacation true bye bye
观看了我们度假真正的再见
bye
再见
you
您